This is the Rabbit R1, one of the most
controversial devices in the past few
years. But, surprisingly, because of a
few recent updates, it quietly became
one of the most powerful productivity
devices on the market right now. So, you
can integrate it with things like Open
Claw or Cloud Code or Hermes, which are
all AI assistants. If you set up now, it
can actually go and do stuff on your
computer, things like summarizing videos
for you, checking your email, pretty
much anything you can think of. How's
the performance of my latest YouTube
[music]
video on YouTube Studio?
>> Views, 14,600 likes, 495 comments, 34
pace.
>> Like, it took 1 to 2 minutes, but you
can imagine for more complex tasks, this
is pretty useful. And in using this,
I've actually found this to be an
amazing form factor. Not only is the
design [music]
super beautiful, because it's designed
by Teenage Engineering, it just makes
sense for a dedicated AI personal
system. You can put this on your desk,
and there's no distractions, there's no
feeds, and you can even put a SIM card
in it to replace your phone with it.